meshbean.com 2013-06-06

# Privacy Policy | Software Publishers & Advertisers - Advertising Software Solution - Make Money Online

### MESHBEAN PRIVACY POLICY

Meshbean makes this Website (the “Site”) available to Users of software from our partnering developers (”Users”), subject to this privacy policy (the “Policy”) and the Meshbean Terms and Conditions. 

This Policy explains what information Meshbean collects about Users on the Site and how Meshbean uses and maintains the information. By becoming a User of Meshbean and using the Site, you signify your acceptance of this Policy. 

IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THE TERMS OF THIS POLICY, IN WHOLE OR IN PART, YOU SHOULD NOT USE THIS SITE OR BECOME A USER. IF YOU ARE A USER AND DO NOT AGREE WITH THE TERMS OF THIS POLICY, YOU MUST IMMEDIATELY TERMINATE YOUR USE IN MESHBEAN. See the “Terminate Account” section below. 

Throughout this Policy we refer to information that can identify you as a specific individual – such as your name, telephone number, email address, as Personally Identifiable Information (”PII”). At Meshbean we take the privacy of our Users and the security of their PII very seriously. 

Meshbean will not collect social security numbers from its Users or Developers. 

You have the right to know what PII we collect, how it is protected and used and the circumstances under which it may be disclosed, and this Policy is designed to provide you with that information. 

This Policy applies only to information collected on the Site and not to information collected or obtained from other sources. 

MeshBean plug-in is an ActiveX control (*.ocx) that adds ad-supported functionality to developer applications. Once it is implemented, Meshbean will display graphical/text banners, pop-under and other types of advertisements on your computer based on the information we collect as stated in this Policy. 

### Note Concerning Users Under 18 Years of Age

The Site, the Meshbean e-mails and the content available in connection therewith, are neither intended for, nor directed to, persons under the age of 18. If Meshbean learns that a person who registers on the Site is under the age of 18, Meshbean will promptly terminate that individual’s Usership. 

### Children’s Privacy

This Site is not open to children. Accordingly, we do not intend to collect PII from anyone we know to be under 13 years of age. 

### Collection of Personally Identifiable Information

Meshbean collects PII in the following ways: 

  * Meshbean can be found from various developer applications across the World Wide Web. Once a User has installed an application, software, program, with Meshbean incorporated into it, Meshbean will track various user search behaviour over each browser session.
  * In addition, Meshbean also reserves the right to use the PII collected to occasionally notify you about important functionality changes to our Site, as well as new services and special offers you may find valuable. You can opt out of these emails during the by accessing the unsubscribe function under the Meshbean Newsletters.

### Use and Sharing of Personally Identifiable Information

Meshbean reserves the right to use PII: 

  * (1) for the specific purpose for which such information was provided; 
  * (2) as disclosed at the time such information is provided; or 
  * (3) as disclosed in this Policy. However, please note that Meshbean.com may change this Policy at any time (See “Changes to this Policy” below), and that therefore Meshbean may in the future use PII for additional purposes not currently included in this Policy. Please check this Policy frequently for this important information. 

Meshbean may share PII (except for photo ID’s, which are never shared with third parties unless required by law) with third parties, including its Partner Sites, parties who advertise on the Site (”Third Party Advertisers”, search partners, sponsors, independent contractors, service providers and marketers, lookup and reference services, and any other entities that Meshbean believes are able to provide Users with special offers and opportunities. Note that although Meshbean advises everyone who receives PII from Meshbean to support this Policy and contractually requires its Third Party Advertisers to treat the PII in accordance with this Policy, Meshbean has no control over such party’s information management practices and is not responsible for any failure of such party to adhere to this Policy. If you do not provide the required PII or do not agree that Meshbean may share your PII with such entities, you may not register as a User, and if you are already a User, you must immediately terminate your use of Meshbean or any applications, software, programs which contains Meshbean. Additionally, Meshbean may share User PII in aggregate, non-personal form, with select companies that wish to reach a particular User target audience. This information will allow these entities to provide relevant offers to a specific group of Users. In the event Meshbean goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your PII will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified by a prominent notice on our Site for 30 days of any such change in ownership or control of your PII. 

Finally, Meshbean reserves the right to disclose PII as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Site. 

### Non-Personally Identifiable Information

Meshbean also collects certain non-personally identifiable information about your web surfing and computer usage, including the non-personally identifiable information more fully described below. 

As is true of most websites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This anonymous technical and statistical information is collected whenever you visit our Site, and we use this information to customize your experience on Meshbean, to help us improve the quality of the Site and make your visits to the Site easy, convenient and fun. 

To deliver Meshbean ads, Meshbean associates the non-personally identifiable information that we collect to an anonymous, randomly-generated User id to create a profile of the categories of products or services in which Users appear to be interested. We may also use information we collect to infer certain User demographic information, such as gender, age range and marital status. Meshbean collects your IP address to help diagnose problems with Meshbean’s server, and to administer this Site. 

We also aggregate anonymous data regarding Users’ online behaviour to better understand how consumers use the Web. To that end, we may use aggregated, anonymous online traffic behaviour to report emerging Web usage trends to the press or to the public or to develop reports for our corporate clients so that they can better understand trends in online consumer behaviour and how those trends relate to their businesses. 

We use cookies and other monitoring technologies to gather anonymous information, as described in more detail below. 

Cookies. Meshbean uses “cookies” on the Site. Cookies are small data files that Meshbean’s server places on an individual’s computer hard drive to enable the individual to more easily communicate and interact with the Site and Meshbean e-mails. For example, Meshbean will place a cookie on a User’s computer when he/she initially registers with the Site. The next time that User visits the Site, Meshbean’s server will recognize the cookie (and the User) and allow the User to play the game immediately without signing in. Cookies also enable us, or our advertisers, to use anonymous behavioral profiles and demographic inferences to increase the relevance of online ads you receive. Some Meshbean ads include “web beacons” and some of our advertisers may include web beacons on some of their web pages at our request. These web beacons allow us to access the cookies we set and provide ad campaign analysis. While some Web browsers allow a User to automatically reject all cookies or be notified when a cookie is about to be placed on the User’s computer, disabling this feature may compromise the efficiency and added services that cookies provide. In the event the Software is uninstalled, no cookies or tracking assets will remain. 

### Linking of Information

Meshbean may combine information provided by a User with information obtained from other sources. Enhancing User files with this other information will allow Meshbean to provide Users with more relevant services, email promotional offers, and direct mail pieces. For example, a User’s user profile will automatically be updated with any information that the User enters on any of the Network Sites. Likewise, any information provided to Meshbean will be used to update the User’s profile on the Network Sites. 

### Security

The security and confidentiality of your PII is extremely important to us. We have implemented technical, administrative and physical security measures to protect PII from unauthorized access and improper use. We keep PII on servers that are protected by firewalls and located in a physically secure facility, accessible only to authorized Meshbean employees. All PII is encrypted using SSL, and we use additional proprietary software to further increase security. From time to time, we review our security procedures in order to consider appropriate new technology and methods. Please be aware though, that, despite our reasonable efforts, no security measures are impenetrable and any connection or information transmitted to Meshbean will be at your own risk. 

### Third Party Cookies

In the course of serving advertisements to this Site, Third Party Advertisers or ad servers may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser. The use of cookies by such Third Party Advertisers or ad servers is not subject to this Policy, but is subject to their own respective privacy policies. 

### Links from the Site

Meshbean provides links to the websites of many of Meshbean’s Third Party Advertisers and Partner Sites. If you link to any of these third party Web sites, this Policy will not apply to your use of, and activities on, those sites. We encourage you to read the legal notices posted on these sites, including their privacy policies. Meshbean shall have no responsibility or liability for your visitation to, and the data collection and use practices of, these sites. All inquiries concerning the use of User PII by a third party must be communicated to that third party, and not to Meshbean. 

### Changes to this Policy

Meshbean may, from time to time, amend this Policy, in whole or part, in its sole discretion. Any changes to this Policy will be effective immediately upon the posting of the revised Policy on the Site. Changes will be reflected by the “Last Updated” reference below. Depending on the materiality of the change, Meshbean may announce the change (1) on the home page of the Site, or (2) provide such notice via e-mail to Users. By continuing to use the Site following any changes or by remaining a User, you will be deemed to have agreed to such changes. 

### QUESTIONS AND CONCERNS

For questions and concerns, please direct your message(s) to [Info@meshbean.com](mailto:Info@meshbean.com)
